const data = [
  {
    question: 'Javascript is an _______ language?',
    id: 0,
    options: [
      'Object-Oriented',
      'Object-Based',
      'Assembly-language',
      'High-level',
    ],
    answer: 'Object-Based',
  },
  {
    question:
      'Which one of the following also known as Conditional Expression:',
    id: 1,
    options: [
      'Alternative to if-else',
      'Switch statement',
      'If-then-else statement',
      'immediate if',
    ],
    answer: 'immediate if',
  },
  {
    question: 'In JavaScript, what is a block of statement?',
    id: 2,
    options: [
      'Conditional block',
      'block that combines a number of statements into a single compound statement',
      'both conditional block and a single statement',
      'block that contains a single statement',
    ],
    answer:
      'block that combines a number of statements into a single compound statement',
  },
  {
    question:
      ' When interpreter encounters an empty statements, what it will do:?',
    id: 3,
    options: [
      'Shows a warning',
      'Prompts to complete the statement',
      'Throws an error',
      'Ignores the statements',
    ],
    answer: 'Ignores the statements',
  },
  {
    question: 'The "function" and " var" are known as:',
    id: 4,
    options: ['Keywords', 'Data types', 'Declaration statements', 'Prototypes'],
    answer: 'Declaration statements',
  },
  {
    question:
      'Which of the following variables takes precedence over the others if the names are the same?',
    id: 5,
    options: [
      'Global variable',
      'The local element',
      'The two of the above',
      'None of the above',
    ],
    answer: 'The local element',
  },
  {
    question:
      'Which one of the following is the correct way for calling the JavaScript code?',
    id: 6,
    options: ['Preprocessor', 'Triggering Event', 'RMI', 'Function/Method'],
    answer: 'Function/Method',
  },
  {
    question: 'Which of the following type of a variable is volatile?',
    id: 7,
    options: [
      'Mutable variable',
      'Dynamic variable',
      'Volatile variable',
      'Immutable variable',
    ],
    answer: 'Mutable variable',
  },
  {
    question:
      'Which of the following option is used as hexadecimal literal beginning?',
    id: 8,
    options: ['00', '0x', '0X', 'Both 0x and 0X'],
    answer: 'Both 0x and 0X',
  },
  {
    question:
      ' When there is an indefinite or an infinite value during an arithmetic computation in a program, then JavaScript prints______.',
    id: 9,
    options: [
      'Prints an exception error',
      'Prints an overflow error',
      'Displays "Infinity"',
      'Prints the value as such',
    ],
    answer: 'Displays "Infinity"',
  },
  {
    question:
      'In the JavaScript, which one of the following is not considered as an error:',
    id: 10,
    options: [
      'Syntax error',
      'Missing of semicolons',
      'Division by zero',
      'Missing of Bracket',
    ],
    answer: 'Division by zero',
  },
];

export default data;
